Communication is a powerful tool in all aspects of our lives,
especially in organisations focused on achieving substantial change.
In this course, you’ll learn how to harness the power of effective communication
to inspire action, both at work and at home.
Meet Aaliyah, Noah and Maryam,
all on their way to work at MODA, an international retailer.
MODA is a market leader with locations on four continents
and is about to embark on a five-year digital transformation.
Aaliyah, the Chief Transformation Officer, will be leading the organisation in this journey.
She’ll identify opportunities to create a standout in-store customer experience.
Noah, the Head of Digital, will be collaborating with Aaliyah
to identify and support new digital transformation opportunities.
Maryam, Lead Analyst, will be working closely with Aaliyah and Noah
to ensure the right data and insights are available.
All three will work as a team to prepare for the transformation
and discover new ways to achieve their individual communication goals.
Throughout this experience, you’ll get the chance to learn more about Aaliyah, Noah and Maryam,
and kick off your own communications journey along with them.